When's your next big birthday?
你的下一个重要生日是什么时候？
How do you feel about that?
你对此感觉如何？
Do you feel you need to do something spectacular to mark it?
你是否觉得需要做些什么了不起的事情来纪念它？
Are you excited by the prospect, or dreading the future?
你对未来感到兴奋，还是感到恐惧？
We usually think of birthdays as a time to celebrate, but they can also cause stress and worry.
我们通常认为生日是庆祝的时刻，但它们也会带来压力和担忧。
Research suggests that this can be even stronger for '9-enders', the 29, 39 and 49-year-olds who are worried about the milestone they are about to reach.
研究表明，对于"9结尾年龄"的人来说，这种感受可能更强烈，即29岁、39岁和49岁的人，他们担心即将达到的人生里程碑。
What is it that makes a number that ends in zero so daunting?
是什么让以零结尾的数字如此令人生畏？
New decades can seem like a fresh start where we evaluate how we are doing.
新的十年似乎是一个新的开始，让我们评估自己的表现。
The problem is that many of us look for something to compare with.
问题是，我们许多人会寻找比较的对象。
This might be people that we know or that we follow on social media, or just what we think society expects us to have achieved by a certain age.
这可能是我们认识的人，或我们在社交媒体上关注的人，或者仅仅是我们认为社会期望我们在某个年龄之前应该取得的成就。
Any differences can lead us to question ourselves.
任何差异都可能导致我们质疑自己。
This links to other stresses that can come with getting older.
这与随着年龄增长而来的其他压力有关。
We might worry that there is limited time to achieve society's expectations.
我们可能会担心达成社会期望的时间有限。
We may also know people from older generations who had health problems at a certain age, and fear that the same thing will affect us.
我们也可能认识上一代到某个年龄段出现健康问题的人，并担心同样的事情会影响到我们。
So, what can we do?
那么，我们能做些什么呢？
Psychologists advise a few steps.
心理学家建议了几个步骤。
Many agree that it's important to celebrate or mark your birthday in your own way.
许多人认为，以自己的方式庆祝或纪念生日很重要。
Do something you genuinely enjoy to avoid feeling the pressure of having to celebrate in a particular way.
做你真正喜欢的事情，以避免被迫以特定方式庆祝的压力。
Another key piece of advice that psychologists offer is that we should use the opportunity to reflect on our lives, but in positive ways.
心理学家提供的另一个关键建议是，我们应该利用这个机会反思我们的生活，但要以积极的方式。
First, consider what you have achieved recently and record those achievements.
首先，想想你最近取得了什么成就，并记录下这些成就。
Then decide what you want to achieve next, and what steps you can take to get there.
然后决定你下一步想要实现什么，以及你可以采取哪些步骤来实现它。
Having achievable goals can help give our lives greater purpose.
拥有可实现的目标有助于给我们的生活带来更大的目标感。
If we can celebrate our successes, set ourselves realistic and achievable goals, and find a way to spend our day that we really enjoy, then maybe we'll find it much easier to deal with those big milestone birthdays.
如果我们能庆祝自己的成功，为自己设定现实且可实现的目标，并找到一种真正享受的方式来度过那一天，那么也许我们会发现应对那些重要的里程碑生日要容易得多。